cashify.in 2019-06-09

# Cashify.in | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains how Cashify ("Cashify," "us," "our," and "we") uses your information and applies to all who use our Website – www.cashify.in, mobile applications, touch technologies, electronic services, social networking sites, interactive features, online services – or any of our described online activities we own or control, including any online activities owned, controlled, or operated by Cashify Affiliates, (collectively, the "Site"). In addition, please review the Site’s Terms of Use which governs your use of the Service, and includes, among other things, grants of rights from you and limits on our liability and your remedies. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with your personal information or interact with the Site.

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by means of a notice on the Site prior to the change becoming effective.

Cashify strives to give the best offers to sell your old gadget; then Cashify refers you to a buyer for your product. We will share your personal information with these carefully selected buyers only when you agree to submit for a quote. This means we do not take your credit card/debit card information and we do not take your money. Registration on Cashify is voluntary; if you do decide to register, we will not share your personal information until you agree to submit to a quote. Subject to your registration, you do get access to certain features, but membership is not necessary to find sale offers. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us.

###### Information We Collect

We collect standard information about Cashify users such as IP addresses, browser type, operating system, device type, what you searched for, referring and exit pages, the dates and times of visits, and other site usage behavior ("Site Visitation Data").Site Visitation Data is used to administer the site and provide general statistics regarding the use of Cashify. We may also use Site Visitation Data to share important updates and information through email & SMS, and also prevent communication that you might not interest you. While selling or registering with our Site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Site to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the section below entitled "Use of cookies and tracking technology" for information about cookies and how we use them.

To help improve our site and services, we may collect certain technical information from your browser software, screen resolution and the website that referred you to us.

###### Sharing information with friends and in user forums

The Cashify allows you to share certain information with friends that you select. Please bear in mind that Cashify cannot control what your friends do with the information you share with them, so you should only share with friends you trust. Once displayed on publicly viewable web pages, information that you share can be collected and used by others. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, please contact us at info@Cashify.in. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Furthermore, if you participate in a user forum on the Cashify website, your comments and your Cashify username will be displayed to all Cashify users on the forum. Cashify is not responsible for what any user or third party may do with information that you choose to share.

We may also provide a feature allowing you to invite a friend to join Cashify. If you provide a friend's email address to us for this reason, we will use that email address only for the purpose of sending a onetime invitation to your friend. Your friend may contact us at info@Cashify.in to remove their information from our database.

###### Use of personal information

We will treat your personal information as confidential, and we will not share your personal information with third parties without your permission, except in the limited circumstances described below. If you accept a referral from Cashify to one of our partner sites, we may provide PII to the partner site to save you having to re-enter that information. When you select a partner site to sell your article(s) to, you must opt in to allow your PII to be submitted to that partner site, and you agree to be bound by their privacy policy as regards use of your PII.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as fulfilling your request for a free shipping kit, purchasing your article(s), or sending confirmation or other emails. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may provide your personal information to our third party marketing partners so they may offer you goods and services which you may find of interest. If you do not wish to receive offers from these third parties, you may unsubscribe from their mailing lists by following the instructions in the offer. If you respond to any such offer, your information will be subject to that third party's privacy policy. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders and to protect and defend the rights and interests of Cashify, its affiliates, suppliers, or users. In the event Cashify goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

We may use and disclose your aggregated usage information with others, in a form that does not identify any inh6idual, to allow Cashify and our advertisers to present targeted advertising to you. We may disclose to third parties, including advertisers and potential business partners, aggregated statistics that we develop from your usage habits, preferences, and history. For example, we may disclose generalized information about usage habits based on aggregated statistics developed from your site usage behaviour and search history. This statistical information will not identify any inh6idual. Registering on Cashify or submission of personal information on any associate or partners channels enables you to receive communication regarding your transaction and any information considered of benefit to you that is sent out from time to time.

We may use your personal information to send you periodic service communication through various forms including but not limited to SMS's, emails, app notifications and any other means for which you have provided credentials in order to receive such communication directly to cashify or through an affiliate, associate or partner of cashify. You will be deemed to have "opted in" to receive such communication unless you request to "opt out" by sending an email to info@Cashify.in or by clicking the unsubscribe button on email communication sent to you.

We will treat your personal information as confidential, and we will not share your personal information with third parties without your permission, except in the limited circumstances described below. If you accept a referral from Cashify to one of our partner sites, we may provide PII to the partner site to save you having to re-enter that information. When you select a partner site to sell your article(s) to, you must opt in to allow your PII to be submitted to that partner site, and you agree to be bound by their privacy policy as regards use of your PII.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as fulfilling your request for a free shipping kit, purchasing your article(s), or sending confirmation or other emails. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

###### Control of personal information

You can confirm, change, delete or update personal information you have provided to us by contacting us at info@Cashify.in.

When you opt-out of promotional communications from us, you may still receive service messages (such as an order confirmation) and legally mandated notices and third party marketing messages Please note that, even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

###### Security of personal information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at info@Cashify.in.

###### Protection of children's privacy

The Site is a general audience site not directed at children under the age of 13.

By using Cashify, you represent that you are at least eighteen years old and understand that you must be at least eighteen years old in order to create an account and purchase the goods or services advertised through the Site. We do not knowingly collect any PII from people under the age of 13. We will promptly delete information associated with any account we obtain actual knowledge is associated with a registered user who is not at least eighteen years old.

###### Use of cookies and tracking technology

Cookies are used in order to better understand how applications and websites work and to optimize online and mobile experiences. Cookies do this by allowing the party serving the cookie to analyse a website’s or mobile app’s performance, to remember user preferences, to recognize whether a computer or device (and probably its user) has visited a website previously, and to serve personalized advertisements. We may collect this information across browsers or devices, but the interest-based advertising cookie is not associated with and does not contain Personal Information.

When you visit our site we may store information about your web session and assign you one or more cookies. Your browser will store these cookies on your computer in a small text file, and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. For example, when you decide to log in as a Cashify member, we store encrypted information in your browser so you don't have to log in on every page. Cookies are not linked to your personal information.

We may also use web beacons, clear gif technology, or action tags as mechanisms to collect aggregate site visitation data by tracking how users navigate to and through our website. We may also use this technology to track the delivery of HTML email messages. Data collected through this mechanism is not linked to personal information.

Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you delete them manually using your browser or operating system software. If you prefer, you can configure your browser to disable cookies or to selectively disable them for some sites. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. 

Cashify works with advertising partners to place advertising on our site. Our third party advertising partners often use a cookie or third party web beacon to track when a click becomes a sale. No PII is ever sent to these advertising partners.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

We use Java script to gather email address entered into the site. When you enter an email address onto the site, we may send periodical reminder emails to that address about items left in a cart. You may opt- out of these emails by following the unsubscribe link in an email.

###### Enforcement of this policy

If you have questions about the policies described in this policy, please contact us directly.

###### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

###### Import Contacts

You can import contacts from email account address books, to invite them to become members of our site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose.

###### Links to other websites

We work with responsible third parties. Their business policies may include different privacy policies and practices than we have. Please be aware that when you click through to third-party websites, our privacy policies no longer apply and that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to review the policies of each site you use.

###### Changes to this policy

We may from time to time update this privacy policy. When we make these updates, we will change the "last updated" date listed below. If we make a material change to this policy in how we use your personal information, we will update users by placing a more prominent notice on our home page before the change. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your use of the Cashify after an updated privacy policy becomes effective will indicate your acceptance of the updated policy.

###### Users from outside India

Cashify is located in India and are subject to the applicable state and federal laws of India. If you use the Cashify, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this privacy policy and subject to such laws.
